<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Becbe Technologies</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Becbe Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON data formatting demo</title>
      <link>/blog/json-formatting-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/json-formatting-demo/</guid>
      <description>This aritle explains about JSON data for more info check here JSONFormatter.dev
 What is JSON? JSON stands for JavaScript Object Notation. It is a text-based representation of structured data that is based on key-value pairs and ordered lists. JSON is commonly, but not exclusively, used to exchange information between web clients and web servers. JSON is derived from JavaScript, and is supported either natively or through libraries in most major programming languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Formatter</title>
      <link>/portfolio/json-formatter-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/json-formatter-dev/</guid>
      <description>JSONFormmater allows to find bugs in JSON data format and fix it quickly.
Most of the users and developers have concerns about online JSON Formatter tools, which may exchange data with servers and there might be the possibility of exposing sensitive data. We ensure all operations are performed within the browser and no network calls or data is exchanged to the server. It gives a peace of mind for any company and developers to trust online tools for day to day work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Python Features That You May Not Be Familiar With</title>
      <link>/blog/top-5-features-of-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/top-5-features-of-python/</guid>
      <description>Python, for all its ease of learning, has some pockets of real complexity. If you’ve ever read through the programming language’s documentation, you’ve probably gotten a sense of that. If you’re new to the language, here are some features you might not be familiar with, but could nonetheless prove useful (or at least fun to experiment with).
Negative Strides on Slices Slices are a fairly modern innovation in several computer languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coursenxt - leading online course platform</title>
      <link>/portfolio/course-nxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/course-nxt/</guid>
      <description>About Coursenxt.com Online platform for free learning.
Learn from the highest rated, most trusted creators on Youtube. Coursenxt has curated content from popular tutorials on Youtube.
 All Analysis Algebra Computers Databases Electronics Literature Networking Programming Web Design
 For more details CourseNxt.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designers thoughts about mobile UI</title>
      <link>/blog/designers-thoughts-about-mobile-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/designers-thoughts-about-mobile-ui/</guid>
      <description>It was originally published in (https://www.interaction-design.org/literature/topics/design-thinking)
What is Design Thinking? Design thinking is a non-linear, iterative process that teams use to understand users, challenge assumptions, redefine problems and create innovative solutions to prototype and test. Involving five phases—Empathize, Define, Ideate, Prototype and Test—it is most useful to tackle problems that are ill-defined or unknown.
In his 2009 TED talk, Design Thinking pioneer Tim Brown discusses Design Thinking’s value in solving extremely complex challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K S Multispeciality Clinic</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ks-multispeciality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ks-multispeciality/</guid>
      <description>About K S Multispeciality Clinic K S Multispeciality Clinic is a Cosmetic/Plastic Surgery Clinic in Bannerghatta Road, Bangalore. The clinic is visited by plastic surgeon like Dr. Kiran Prasad N V. The timings of K S Multispeciality Clinic are: Mon-Sat: 09:30-23:00 and Sun: 09:30-13:00. Some of the services provided by the Clinic are: Breast Augmentation/Mammoplasty,Wart Removal,Burn Surgery,Botox Injections and Liposuction &amp;amp; Sculpting etc.
For more details KS Multispeciality</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin MultiPlatform</title>
      <link>/blog/kotlin-multi-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/kotlin-multi-platform/</guid>
      <description>The most obvious benefit of cross-platform mobile development: cost savings. Simply put, using the same tools to simultaneously build an app for iOS and Android will save you time and money over using different toolsets to build those app versions sequentially.
Cross-platform systems such as Flutter, Xamarin and React Native will let you avoid a lot of duplicated work and might only cost you, say, between 1.2x and 1.5x more than if you hadn’t pursued cross-platform development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>