<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recents Article on Becbe Technologies</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recents Article on Becbe Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON data formatting demo</title>
      <link>/blog/json-formatting-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Sep 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/json-formatting-demo/</guid>
      <description>This aritle explains about JSON data for more info check here JSONFormatter.dev
 What is JSON? JSON stands for JavaScript Object Notation. It is a text-based representation of structured data that is based on key-value pairs and ordered lists. JSON is commonly, but not exclusively, used to exchange information between web clients and web servers. JSON is derived from JavaScript, and is supported either natively or through libraries in most major programming languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Python Features That You May Not Be Familiar With</title>
      <link>/blog/top-5-features-of-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/top-5-features-of-python/</guid>
      <description>Python, for all its ease of learning, has some pockets of real complexity. If you’ve ever read through the programming language’s documentation, you’ve probably gotten a sense of that. If you’re new to the language, here are some features you might not be familiar with, but could nonetheless prove useful (or at least fun to experiment with).
Negative Strides on Slices Slices are a fairly modern innovation in several computer languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designers thoughts about mobile UI</title>
      <link>/blog/designers-thoughts-about-mobile-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/designers-thoughts-about-mobile-ui/</guid>
      <description>It was originally published in (https://www.interaction-design.org/literature/topics/design-thinking)
What is Design Thinking? Design thinking is a non-linear, iterative process that teams use to understand users, challenge assumptions, redefine problems and create innovative solutions to prototype and test. Involving five phases—Empathize, Define, Ideate, Prototype and Test—it is most useful to tackle problems that are ill-defined or unknown.
In his 2009 TED talk, Design Thinking pioneer Tim Brown discusses Design Thinking’s value in solving extremely complex challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin MultiPlatform</title>
      <link>/blog/kotlin-multi-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/kotlin-multi-platform/</guid>
      <description>The most obvious benefit of cross-platform mobile development: cost savings. Simply put, using the same tools to simultaneously build an app for iOS and Android will save you time and money over using different toolsets to build those app versions sequentially.
Cross-platform systems such as Flutter, Xamarin and React Native will let you avoid a lot of duplicated work and might only cost you, say, between 1.2x and 1.5x more than if you hadn’t pursued cross-platform development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>