<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on Becbe Technologies</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on Becbe Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:19:35 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JSON Formatter</title>
      <link>/portfolio/json-formatter-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/json-formatter-dev/</guid>
      <description>JSONFormmater allows to find bugs in JSON data format and fix it quickly.
Most of the users and developers have concerns about online JSON Formatter tools, which may exchange data with servers and there might be the possibility of exposing sensitive data. We ensure all operations are performed within the browser and no network calls or data is exchanged to the server. It gives a peace of mind for any company and developers to trust online tools for day to day work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>coursenxt - leading online course platform</title>
      <link>/portfolio/course-nxt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/course-nxt/</guid>
      <description>About Coursenxt.com Online platform for free learning.
Learn from the highest rated, most trusted creators on Youtube. Coursenxt has curated content from popular tutorials on Youtube.
 All Analysis Algebra Computers Databases Electronics Literature Networking Programming Web Design
 For more details CourseNxt.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K S Multispeciality Clinic</title>
      <link>/portfolio/ks-multispeciality/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/ks-multispeciality/</guid>
      <description>About K S Multispeciality Clinic K S Multispeciality Clinic is a Cosmetic/Plastic Surgery Clinic in Bannerghatta Road, Bangalore. The clinic is visited by plastic surgeon like Dr. Kiran Prasad N V. The timings of K S Multispeciality Clinic are: Mon-Sat: 09:30-23:00 and Sun: 09:30-13:00. Some of the services provided by the Clinic are: Breast Augmentation/Mammoplasty,Wart Removal,Burn Surgery,Botox Injections and Liposuction &amp;amp; Sculpting etc.
For more details KS Multispeciality</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>